It's hot! It's hot! Hot!
Good morning!
Oh, isn't it bad? Oh, wait!
Oh, man, this might be the best day of my life.
Wow!
Oh, this is it!
BGM.
Yay!
Wait, wait, wait!
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit! Eww! I'll get pimples! Look, honey! Bon appétit!
I'll get pimples.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Yeah, it feels really good.
Yummy?
Delicious!
It's my favorite Japanese confectionery.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy!
Well, the show starts at 6:00 p.m., but here's what's different about our show.
First of all, we only have a part of the show.
So we'll start before noon.
So we'll be coming in a little before noon, and we'll be able to prepare for just that one part of the show.
So we can prepare a lot for that part of the show.
It's a different feeling than usual.
Everyone feels like they are on a field trip.
I understand how you feel. It's a mess.
You're going to be used for the rest of your life. You're a blacklister.
I'm not a photographer.
What? I'm just gesturing.
What is that? I don't know what a gesture is.
Half of them.
What does it mean?
You know what I mean? You know what I mean.
Half a number.
You know, like that goat...
Once it rots and they swallow it.
And they can't digest it as it is.
So they chew it up and put it back in.
And put it back in the goat's mouth.
Chew it again and swallow it.
Half.
Half?
I'm sure.
Right? I'm sure.
I was just doing this when no one else knew.
Oh, my God.
This is a stage.
You can see the stage...
Oh, but we're working on it.
I'm probably not gonna be able to do it right now.
Okay, then.
Let's just go out there and hit the people walking around.
Oh, man, get on with it.
I'm scared of what I'm feeling today.
Wait a minute.
Djembs.
They're nibbling on it.
How did you get this on stage?
How did this get on stage?
Hey! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
No!
Not here.
Let's move.
Can I stand here?
I'm gonna need you to take a screencap of this.
Edit it out.
I'll have him take a shot of it, and then we'll edit it out, and then we'll go from there.
I'll see it in three seconds.
Let me play Aihara.
All right.
Theater Company
Wow!
Isshin-kun standing on the stage is so cool
No, my honey.
I'm cooler than you.
No, you're cooler.
I'm jealous!
I'm going home.
・・・・・・ follow my charisma everyone Fire!
Condition.
Well...
If this bottle is 100% full.
If it's 100% full, it's 100% full.
Well...
I guess that's about right.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to get heartbroken.
I'm going to be deeply scarred.
We're going to make a documentary from here on out.
Yes, sir.
I'm going away.
Solo, right?
Yes, sir.
Yes, on this side of the stage.
Um...
Yes.
It's like a documentary.
What does One Love One Heart mean to you?
One Love One Heart for me.
One Love One Heart for me
It's like the devil and Kanabo
It's like me to Rubuta and Toketoke Red Blue.
I think Love One needs me.
Please tell us about the highlights of this live show.
We are going to play all the songs from the second album.
There are so many great songs on the second album.
There are so many great songs on it.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I think we are
In this title
That there is no limit to what we can do
We don't have any wishes.
I hope we were able to convey that to everyone.
Interview
I would like to interview you.
How many friends do you have?
Friends?
Very realistic.
How many friends do you have?
Friends.
Where do you go from here?
If you're just barely friends, I'm like your BFF.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I'm just doing a normal pre-production interview.
Please, please, let me be... - Sis...
I'm not going to do anything I wouldn't do well.
It's okay, Yajima-san.
That way? That way?
Me, too.
I already took a bunch of pictures before rehearsal.
Then we're good for today.
Okay.
I don't have to.
But... since you're here, I didn't.
Turn around.
The library.
You can scream in the library!
We have the whole place to ourselves, so we can be loud.
And it's a university.
Here's a book about what we're doing.
They're really good at it.
That's great.
Ta-da!
Wow, Haruma reads to her, and yes, they do this. They are so close to each other. That's great. Ta-da!
Amazing.
Okay, Haruma, read to them.
Once upon a time.
I'll be called the singing brother.
That's fine. You're going for it, right?
I'm going for it.
Cat, cat, mama cat.
It came trotting in.
Show us the picture. It's a picture book.
Cat, cat, kitten.
toddle and toddle.
Yes, OK.
Worst
It's not bad.
Not so bad!
Filming
We're filming!
Grandma? Are you wearing a uniform? We're filming high school students.
What?
She's wearing a uniform? High school. What grade do you look like in high school?
Fourteenth grade.
That's stupid.
I am. I really am.
Fourteenth grade.
No, really.
Senior year.
Why not?
I think I'm a total high-schooler.
You feel like a total high schooler, Miu?
Yeah!
What's the difference?
Skeletal structure?
An old lady's bone structure.
No way!
That's enough.
You're lying.
I miss the old days!
Uniforms are so nice!
Uniforms are great!
I love seifuku!
So cute!
Impossible! It's too cute!
Let's put hearts on it too!
It's so cute!
It's so cute. It really is.
I think it's good.
Scary, it looks good on you.
Say, Ishii, too.
You too, Ishii.
Oh, you don't get it.
Are you scared?
Scared? Oh, no.
This one is cute.
Oh, wow, it's nice. It's really good.
Don't look at me.
Don't look at me. You scared me. Don't look at me, don't look at me!
You scared me.
I'm not looking at you.
Don't look at me.
I'm not leaking that much.
I'm leaking a lot.
No, I'm not.
You're just being cute.
Oh, my God.
Okay, I'm gonna do my makeup with this.
What are you doing? I could see your pores and everything.
Do you see much?
Not at all.
Okay, that's enough.
Camera mark.
There it is! Bogey!
Okay, that's enough.
Okay.
Oh, fuck it.
Oh, shit, I can't do it. I can't do it.
Let's play baseball.
Who's there? Who?
Let's go play basketball. Who? Who? - I'm gonna catch up with you.
Let's play basketball.
Oh, my God.
A day in the life of baseball.
Okay, I'm home.
I'm done with the first take for now, but...
This place is so nice.
It looks like something out of an anime or drama, so cute!
It's so cute!
Is it on film?
They're selling adorable things.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I want one!
This is the first novel I ever read.
This is pretty.
This is cute.
It's got a lot of words in it.
I feel like it's going to make me smarter.
I'll do my best.
Go home.
He said it's a shopping arcade.
This way, right?
Where are you going this time?
To the Plaza.
I'm going to the Plaza.
Shopping.
Shopping at Prada.
Prada, Gucci and Balenciaga.
I want to go shopping!
Yay!
I'm not buying anything.
Shoes, sunglasses, bags, clothes, accessories.
And wisdom, power, wealth, and fame? Yeah. Shoes, sunglasses, bags, clothes, accessories...
And that's it.
And wisdom, and power, and wealth, and fame.
What? You got everything in the world.
The man who has it all, the man who has it all...
Monkey.
Okay, well, uh, that's where the goal ends.
Hi, I'm Kyu-chan.
Yes, thank you for your time.
I think the last Fireworks was about love.
This time, it was about my future.
I've grown up one step more.
I've grown up a step more since Fireworks.
You can see us in the roles of these children,
I wonder what it's called, it's amazing, I wonder what it's about, I think students can probably relate to the content quite well.
I didn't expect it to be a continuation of Fireworks, but it was a music video that was kind of in the same world line.
I'm going to study abroad in the U.S. for a year.
And I'm going to study abroad to study acting, so...
This story is very exciting.
This is a munecycle story that can only be told now.
I hope everyone will watch it and think about it.
I want you to look at it, think about it, and think about who it is and what it's like.
Please watch a lot.
The dance moves are also very story-like and a bit difficult, but I hope you will all try to imitate them and dance along.
I would be very happy if you could imitate the dances.
Well, let's see....
Me and Koei are on a basketball team.
We are on the basketball team.
And we're on the basketball team.
We're playing 1v1, I think.
Well, you know, Koei was really good.
Well, Koei is here.
Koei is smiling so much!
Ha-ha-ha!
Well, Koei was really good, wasn't he?
So I want to become a good basque artist so that I can beat Koei.
Well, it was a two-day shoot.
Well, we had to shoot for two days because of the weather and other reasons, but...
But it was the first time for me to do something like this for two days.
I wondered how it would turn out.
But since it was divided into two days, we were able to shoot on the first and second days with a little more time to spare.
I was able to enjoy the shoot more than last time, so I'm very happy about that.
After a hard day of muscle training, we talked about our dreams.
After training hard, we talked about our dreams with our backs to each other.
It was a pretty heated conversation.
There's a scene where they were talking about getting married or something.
Please guess where!
I play the role of a high school sophomore.
I'm the only sophomore in high school.
I was very happy to be able to play a role at my age.
I would be happy if you could enjoy the scenes where we all get together and work hard, as well as the feeling that only high school students can have fun.
I'll be happy if you do.
I think the scene where they are making the album with all their hearts, sitting around the desk and decorating it....
I was decorating it and putting stickers on it.
I was decorating it and putting stickers on it and so on.
It was really like we were just being ourselves.
I felt like it was something you would see at school during recess.
It was like what it would be like if we were members of this group at school.
I think that was the highlight of the show.
It's a sequel to Fireworks, so the theme of this year's episode was also about adolescence,
Last time, the theme was about love, but this time, I don't know what it was about.
It's not a love story.
It's a different kind of coming-of-age.
I can remember my youth differently from the love story.
It was a bit nostalgic, like I remember such conflicts.
It made me nostalgic.
There was something very...
There was something different again, so there were a lot of things that were different.
The atmosphere was different.
Before, it was like we were all together.
This time it's like each one's own little station.
I was really excited to see the two connected.
I simply thought that everyone's albums were so cute
I thought it reminded me of them.
It's so amazing!
Yesterday and today, for two days
I was so nervous because I thought it was going to be a lot of work, but
But it was such a fun two days!